Henry-Russell Hitchcock
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Chronological Name and Subject Files, 1919-1987, Series 2:; (Boxes 1-22; 21.9 linear ft.)
  Association of Collegiate Schools of Architecture (1949, 1954)
  Atelier (1951)
  Athenaeum of Philadelphia (1969-1970, 1977-1978, 1980-1981, 1983, 1985)
  Atkin, William Wilson (1958)
  Atkinson, Fello (1950-1959, 1961-1967, 1969, 1971-1973, 1977-1978, 1980, 1982)
  Atkinson, G. A. (1961, 1969)
  Atkinson, George (1955)
  Atomic Energy Commission of Canada (see: Canada, Atomic Energy Commission of)
  Auden, W. H. (1952-1953)
  Aufsberg, Lala (1958, 1965-1967, 1971-1972)
  Aurora Zanichelli (1955)
  Austin, A. Everett [Chick] (1953, 1957, 1984)
  Austin, A. Everett [Chick] and Helen (1952)
  Austin Art Center (1965) (see also: Trinity College)
  Austin, David (1966)
  Austin, Helen (1948, 1950, 1956, 1958, 1960, 1965-1968, 1970, 1973, 1986, undated)
  Austin, Mollie (1961)
  Austin, Sarah G. (1979)
  Australian Journal of Art (1978)
  Authors Club (1962)
  Auzas, Pierre-Marie (1965-1967, 1979-1980)
  Avenue (1985)
  Avery, Elizabeth P. (l950)
  Avery Library, Columbia University (1951, 1973-1974, 1977, 1981) (see also: Columbia University)
  Avery, Peter (1965)
  Avery Study Center, Columbia University (1982) (see also: Columbia University)
  Avis Rent-a-Car (1961)
  Azelle, Robert (1955)
  "B. 1955" (2 pocket calendars) (1955)
  Bacon, Leonard Lee (1970)
  Bacon, Mardges (1984)
  Baga, Khalid (1979)
  Baggage Declaration (1945)
  Bailey, James and Gordon, Inc. (1957-1962, 1964)
  Bailey's Studio (1946)
  Baker (1957)
  Baker, Joseph (1960)
  Baker, Roger (1953)
  Bakewell, Hester Adams (1970)
  Baldinger, Wallace S. (1949)
  Baldwin, Deborah (1985)
  Baldwin, Raymond E. (1945)
  Baldwin, Susan (1976)
  Ball, Mr. and Mrs. William Burnham (undated)
  Ballard, Mary (1974)
  Ballman, Lucille (1949)
  Balmoral Castle (1952, 1954)
  Baltimore City Museum (1952) (see also: Peale Museum)
  Baltimore Museum of Art (1948)
  Baltimore Sun (1968) (see also: Sun) (1968)
  Banham, Reyner (Peter) (1956, 1959, 1961-1962, 1972-1973)
  Banham, Reyner (Peter) and Mary (1958)
  Banker, Douglas (1977)
  Banking (1965-1966, 1970-1971)
  Bannister, Turpin C. (1941, 1943-1945, 1947, 1950-1952, 1954-1956, 1958, undated)
  Bantam Books (1962)
  Bar, D. D. (1969)
  Barbarosa, Jorge de Castro (1957)
  Barber, Leila (1966)
  Barclay, Jo (1953)
  Barclay's Bank (1945-1948, 1950, 1952-1955, 1957-1958, 1960-1961, 1972)
  Bardwell, Helen H. (1955)
  Barley, M. W. (1952)
  Barman, Christian (1951)
  Barnard College (1954-1957, 1965)
  Barnes, Anthony (1952)
  Barnes, Charles D. (1968)
  Barnes, Cynthia (1962)
  Barnes, Henry (1952)
  Barnlund, Mr. and Mrs. D. C. (1949)
  Barnstone, Howard (1953, 1958, 1960-1961)
  Baron, Docteur Lucien (1927)
  Barr, Alfred H. (1928, 1930-1932, 1937, 1945, 1954, 1973, 1981, undated)
  Barr, Marga (Daisy) (1957, 1959, 1961, 1978, 1983, 1985, undated)
  Barrall, Xavier (1976)
  Barrand, H. (1955)
  Barrett, John (1956)
  Barsee, L. (1976)
  Barton, Eleanor (1949, 1955-1956, 1959, 1965)
  Baskin, Leonard and Lisa (1969)
  Batsford, Ltd. (1941, 1948-1953, 1955-1957)
  Battle, Governor (1955)
  Bauch, K. (1966)
  Bauer, A. (1928)
  Bauer, Catherine (1940)
  Bauhaus Archiv (1963)
  Baumann, Christopher (1946)
  Baume, Henry B. (1956-1957)
  Bayer, Adolf (1963)
  Bayer, Herbert (1954)
  Bayer, Julia (1945, 1952)
  Bayley, J. B. (1946, 1952)
  Bayley, John (1953)
  Bayley, Stephen (1974)
  Beardall Fenton and Co. (1969)
  Beatty, C. J. P. (1962)
  Beck, Andy (1976)
  Beck, Haig (1979)
  Beckwith (1964)
  Bedenkapp, John (1952-1956, 1959)
  Beeton, M. (1946)
  Beggs, Thomas (1946)
  Belding, Ann (1950-1951)
  Bell, Herbert C. F. (1946, 1948-1949, 1957-1958)
  Bell, Janet M. (1952)
  Bellotto (1960)
  Belluschi (1954-1956)
  Beloit College (1945)
  Belz, Carl (1972)
  Benda, E. (1931)
  Bender, Angela (1966)
  Bendixson, T.M.P. (1961)
  Benero, Herbert W. (1955)
  Benes, Miroslava (1975)
  Benesch, Otto (1946, 1956)
  Benesch, Otto and Eva (1947, 1959)
  Bennett, Gordon C. (1946)
  Bennett Books (1950)
  Bennett, Richard M. (1939)
  Bennett, Mrs. Roger Williams (1962)
  Bennington College (1953, 1957)
  Benson, Elizabeth (1962)
  Benson, John Howard (1952-1954)
  Benson, Robert Alan (1968)
  Benton, Charlotte (1978)
  Benton, Tim (1974)
  Berenson, Bernard (1931)
  Bergdoll, Barry (1979-1982, 1984)
  Berger, Maurice (1978)
  Bergeron, Claude (1967)
  Berlin (1956, 1964, 1975)
  Berlin, Technische Universitat (1966)
  Berman, Eugene (Genya) (1931-1932, 1945, 1969)
  Berman, Leonide (1931, undated)
  Bermudez, Luis (1955)
  Bernett, Dick (1950)
  Bernett, F. A. (1959, 1963-1965, 1968)
  Bernett, Frederick (1961)
  Bernett, P. A. (1967)
  Bernier, Rosamond (1955)
  Berrill, Maurice (1958, 1958)
  Berry-Hill Galleries (1971, 1981)
  Betjeman, John (1946, 1952, 1956)
  Bett, Regina (1966-1967)
  Bevan, Roger (1978)
  Beyer, Klaus G. (1970-1971)
  Bialostocki, Jan (1968, 1970-1971, 1973, 1985)
  Bicknell, Minnette (1975)
  Bicknell, Peter (1965)
  Biederman, Charles (1978)
  Bielfeld Kunsthalle (1968-1970, 1973-1975, 1985) (see also: Kunsthalle Bielfeld)
  Biennale (1959-1960)
  Bier, Julius (1953)
  Bildarchiv (1956)
  Billcliff, Roger (1971)
  Bills, Paid (1965-1970)
  Binet, Ann (1955)
  Birkhams, Martin (1960)
  Birmingham Public Library (1946)
  Birrell, J. P. (1963)
  Birthday (1978, 1980, 1983, 1985)
  Bischoff, Ralph F. (1946)
  Bissell, Elaine (1951)
  Bixley, Grace (1954)
  Blach, Peter (1939)
  Blackheath Society (1955)
  Blackman, Audrey (1962-1963)
  Blake, Sarah (1966)
  Blanch, M. (1958)
  Blanckenhagen, Peter H. von (1979)
  Blau, Eve M. (1978-1984)
  Bletter, Rosemarie (1981-1982)
  Bliss, Eleanor (1945, 1947-1953, 1959-1960, 1963, 1967, 1972, 1974-1975, 1978, 1981, undated)
  Bliss, Robert (1963)
  Bliss, Mr. and Mrs. Robert Woods (1958)
  Bloch, Stella Rubenstein (undated)
  Blond, Anthony (1962)
  Bloom, Florence and William (1964-1965)
  Blue Cross/Blue Shield (1963, 1982, 1985) (see also: Medicare/Blue Shield)
  Blume, Marcia (1960-1961)
  Blunt, Anthony (1946)
  Blyth, R. Henderson (1947-1948)
  Boardman, Jane Carrott (1969)
  Boas, George (1954)
  Boase, T.S.R. (1957)
  Bobbs Merrill Co. (1966, 1968, 1971)
  Bober, Harry (1955, 1957)
  Bodine, Thomas R. (1973)
  Boggs, Jean (1952, 1957, 1960, 1962)
  Bohan, Peter J. (1957, 1963)
  Bohdan, Carol (1971)
  Boissonnas (1927)
  Bollingen Foundation, Inc. (1956, 1960)
  Bolschwig, Otto A. (1927) (see also: Van Bolschwig, Otto A.)
  Bolton and Fairhead, Ltd. (1946-1947)
  Bond van Nederlandsche Architecten (1956)
  Bonet Gari, Luis (1972-1973)
  Bonn (1963-1964)
  Bony, Jean (1956)
  Bonython, John (1966)
  Book Land (1963)
  Boothby, Norman B. (1952)
  Booziotis, Bill (1959)
  Borgenecht Gallery (1961)
  Borges, Max (1956)
  Born, Ernest (1952)
  Bornecque, Jacques-Henry (1955)
  Borowski and Co. (1970)
  Boschma, C. (1963)
  Bose, Konrad (1953-1954)
  Boston Albany Railroad (1963)
  Boston Architecture Center (1949, 1966)
  Boston Arts Festival (1954)
  Boston Athenaeum (1950-1951)
  Boston College (1975)
  Boston, Municipal Court of (1966)
  Boston, Museum of Fine Arts (1945, 1947-1950, 1967, 1969, 1975, 1982) (see also: Museum of Fine Arts, Boston)
  Boston Public Library (1955)
  Boston Redevelopment Authority (1964, 1967)
  Boston Society of Independent Artists (1950)
  Boston University (1954, 1963, 1968)
  Botz, H. (1969)
  Bourgeois, Victor (1953)
  Boutmy, P. de (1956)
  Bouton, Margaret (1949)
  Bouverie, David Pleydell (1945, 1950, 1952-1953, 1955, 1965, 1972-1973, 1975) (see also: Pleydell-Bouverie, David)
  Bowdin College (1973-1974)
  Bowen, Carroll G. (1960)
  Bowler, Fairchild (1955)
  Boyd, Robin (1966)
  Boyden, Mary (1952)
  Boyer, Christine (1983)
  Boyle, Michael (1970)
  Brackett, Jeffrey R. (1935)
  Bradley, John (1957)
  Bradley, Prentice (1954)
  Bramm, Vincent (1974)
  Brandeis University (1961)
  Brandl, Ernest H. (1946-1947, 1959-1961)
  Brandon, Harvey (1970, 1981)
  Brandon-Jones, John (1955-1956, 1960)
  Branner, Robert (1964-1966)
  Brasher, Louise Tharaud (1979)
  Braxton, Anne (1968)
  Brazil (1957)
  Braziller, George (1959-1961, 1966, 1972)
  Brena, Francisco (Paco) (1982-1983)
  Brendel, Otto J. (1950)
  Brentano Books (1941, 1946)
  Brett, Lionel (1953, 1955)
  Bretter, Ernest (1955)
  Brewer, Charles (1961)
  Brewer, Gussie (1946)
  Brewer, Helen (1959)
  Brewer, Joseph (1928, 1935-1938, 1940-1941, 1944-1961, 1964, 1967, 1969, 1971-1973, 1984)
  Brewer, Warren and Putnam, Inc. (1932)
  Brewster, E. W. (1946)
  Brewster, Margaret F. (1946)
  Briggs, Rose T. (1947, 1949-1954, 1963-1964, 1973, 1978, 1981)
  Bright, William E. (1959)
  Brighton Corp. (1958)
  Brion-Guerry, L. (1971)
  Bristol Society of Architects (1951)
  Bristol, University of (1963, 1965-1967)
  Britannica Encyclopedia (1953) (see also: Encyclopedia Britannica)
  British Book Center (1951-1952)
  British Broadcasting Corporation (1955, 1969, 1974-1975)
  British Committee for the Interchange of Teachers (1951-1952, 1955)
  British Council (1960)
  British Council in the Netherlands (1952)
  British Information Services (1945, 1951)
  British Ministry of War Transport (1945, undated)
  British Museum (1950)
  Britton, Coby (1972)
  Broadfoot, Winston (1976-1977)
  Brockhaus Fine Arts (1974)
  Brocklebank, Mr. and Mrs. Charles (1986)
  Brocklebank, Marcia Early (Mrs. Charles) (1966, 1973, 1977-1978)
  Brockunier, S. H. (1952)
  Broderick, Mosette Glaser (1974-1977, 1979-1981, 1985-1986)
  Brodrick, Peter (1949-1957, undated)
  Brokaw, Chloe (1961)
  Brooklyn Museum (1945, 1963, 1967, 1977)
  Brooks, H. Allen (1953, 1956, 1958-1983)
  Brotz, Howard (1963-1964, 1966, 1979)
  Brown, Betty (1960)
  Brown, Charles H. (1958, 1962)
  Brown, Donald H. (1955-1956)
  Brown, Eric (1949)
  Brown, Blanche (1972)
  Brown, Elizabeth Miles (1977)
  Brown, Mrs. Leonard M. (1967)
  Brown, Margaret (1949, 1951)
  Brown, Milton W. (1957, 1976)
  Brown, Robert (1970, 1974-1975)
  Brown, Theodore (1956)
  Brown University (1982)
  Brown, William E. (1955)
  Browne, Mrs. Douglas (1952)
  Brownstone Revival Committee of New York City (1969-1970)
  Bruccoli, Matthew (1965)
  Brun, Jean-Pierre (1973)
  Brunet, Peirre (1956)
  Brunner, Bob (1962)
  Brussels (1972)
  Bryan, John Albury (1970)
  Bryan, Polly (1959)
  Bryant, Helen P. (1962)
  Bryn Mawr College (1973-1974)
  Bucarelli, Palma (1965)
  Bucher, Francois (1960)
  Buchholz Gallery (1948)
  Buchman, Joan (1968)
  Buck, Robert L. (1982)
  Buckley, Charles E. (1964, 1971)
  Buckman, Louise (1950)
  Buddensieg, Tilmann (1978)
  Buell, Irwin A. (1948)
  Buffalo Academy of Fine Arts (1939, 1982)
  Buffalo Architectural Guidebook (1979, 1981-1982)
  Building Design (1974)
  Building Magazine (1951)
  Built in the U.S.A. (1952)
  Bull, Harry (1946)
  Bulloch, O. M. (1956)
  Bulloche, J. E. (1955)
  Bullock (1978)
  Bulloz (1958)
  Bunce, John (1954)
  Bunce, Nellie (1955, 1959, 1968, 1973, 1979-1980, 1986)
  Bunschaft, Gordon (1956)
  Bunting, Bainbridge (1967)
  Burchard, John Ely (1947, 1951-1952, 1956, 1962)
  Burden, William A. M. (1955)
  Burdon-Muller, Rowland (1948-1952)
  Burg, Hermann and Margaret (1946)
  Burg, John (1958)
  Burke, Anne (1962-1964, 1967-1970, undated)
  Burke, Joseph (1954-1958)
  Burnham, Alan (1942, 1937, 1956-1957, 1970)
  Burnham, Frances B. ( 1953)
  Burnham Library, Art Institute of Chicago (1945, 1971) (see also: Ryerson and Burnham Libraries; Art Institute of Chicago; Chicago, Art Institute of)
  Burns, Howard (1968)
  Burns, John (1952, 1983)
  Burroughs, T.H.B. (1967)
  Burton, Christopher (1963)
  Burton, Emily (1952)
  Burton, Michael (1953, 1956)
  Bush, Lucile (1965)
  Bush, Martin H. (1963)
  Bush-Brown, Albert (1952, 1956-1958, 1977)
  Bush-Brown, Harold (1954, 1965)
  Butler, Jeanne F. (1972)
  Butler, L. D. (1967)
  Butler, Ruth (1957)
  Butterfield, Victor (1945, 1947)
  Butterick, George F. (1978)
  Cabral, Edward (1980)
  Cadbury-Brown, John (1955)
  Cadbury-Brown, H. T. (Jim) (1956, 1958)
  Cahill, Fred V. (1957)
  Cahn, Elizabeth (1977)
  Calder, Sandy (1938, 1955-1956)
  Caldwell, Ian (1975-1976)
  Calendars (see: B.1955)
  California (1965)
  California Institute of Technology (1948-1949)
  California Palace of the Legion of Honor (1950)
  California, San Jose State University (1979)
  California, University of (1951-1952, 1961, 1964, 1966-1967, 1971, 1973, 1976, 1980)
  Callisen, Sterling A. (1941)
  Callisen, Sterling A. and Sally (1945)
  Cambridge [Mass.] Historical Society (1967)
  Cambridge University (1962, 1964, 1966)
  Campagnie Francaise d'Aeronautiques (1956)
  Campanella, Gaspare (1970)
  Campbell, Colin G. (1978)
  Campbell, Malcolm (1975)
  Canada, Atomic Energy Commission of (1973)
  Canada Council (1971)
  Canada, National Archives of (1956)
  Canada, National Gallery of (1926, 1960)
  Canada, Royal Architectural Institute of (1960)
  Canfield, Abigail and Cass (1975)
  Canner and Co. (1949)
  Caples, Sara Elizabeth (1969-1970)
  Car (European) (1965)
  Car (1966)
  Cardiff Public Library (1946)
  Carey, Jane F. (1973)
  Carey T. (1973)
  Carlhian, Jean Paul (1952-1953, 1966, 1971, 1973)
  Carling, E .B. (1947-1948)
  Carlisle, Anna (1956)
  Carlson, Ralph (1979)
  Carnegie Book Shop (1952)
  Carnegie Institute (1955, 1985)
  Carnegie Institute of Technology (1947, 1954)
  Carpenter, G. R. (1946)
  Carpenters Company of Philadelphia (1973)
  Carr, Gerald (1968)
  Carre Gallerie (1947-1949)
  Carrington, Robert (1953, 1970)
  Carroll, Martha 1975
  Carrott, Richard G. (1955-1956, 1959-1963, 1965, 1967-1969, 1971-1979, 1981-1986)
  Carter, Amon E. (1960)
  Carter Foundation (1961)
  Carter, Lady Bonham (1956)
  Carter, Edward C. (Bobby) (1926, 1944-1948, 1960)
  Carter, Ernestine (1947, 1952, 1962-1963, 1968, 1978-1979, 1983) (see also: Carter, John and Ernestine)
  Carter, Gwendolyn (1952)
  Carter, John 1941, (1946, 1948, 1952, 1954, 1959)
  Carter, John and Ernestine (1936, 1945) (see also: Carter, Ernestine)
  Carter, Norman F. (1952, 1954, 1959)
  Casabella-Continuita (1961, 1965)
  Casanelles, Enric (1959)
  Cascieri, Arcangelo (1954)
  Case Western Reserve University (1972-1973)
  Cassidy, Victor M. (1974)
  Cassilly, Carolyn (1974)
  Casson, Hugh (1948, 1955)
  Cassy, Edmund J. (1964)
  Cast Iron Architecture, Friends of (1970, 1973-1974)
  Castano Galleries (1963)
  Castro, Dicken (1955-1957, 1960-1961)
  Catholic University of America (1963)
  Catlin, Stanton L. (1952, 1956)
  Catsoulis, Evangelos (1981, 1983)
  Causey, Andrew (1983)
  Cavanagh, Tom R. (1949)
  Cement and Concrete Association (1954)
  Center for Inter-American Relations (1969)
  Central Corporate Library (1960)
  Central Council for the Care of Churches (1955)
  Central National Bank of Middletown (1946)
  Central Office of Information (1955-1956)
  Centrum (1963)
  Century Association (1972-1973, 1975-1977, 1979-1980, 1982, 1984)
  Cetto, Max L. (1960)
  Chafee, D. S. (1984)
  Chafee, Richard (1969, 1974, 1976-1978)
  Chalfont, Randolph (1962-1963)
  Chambers Encyclopedia (1946-1949, 1954, 1961-1963)
  Chapin, Betty (1981)
  Chapin, Betty and Schuyler G. (1975, 1982)
  Chapman, Edward (1952-1953)
  Chapman, Rosamund (1957)
  Charette (1963)
  Charney, W. Mick (1977)
  Chattey, Paul W. (1983)
  Cheek, Leslie (1946-1948, 1953, 1984)
  Cheek, Richard (1978-1979)
  Chelmsford and District Chapter, Society of Architects (1962)
  Cheltham, Charles (1962, 1964)
  Chermayeff, Serge (1939, 1946-1948, 1950, 1954)
  Chernow, Barbara (1982)
  Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Co. (1948)
  Chevojon Freres (1956, 1958)
  Chicago Architectural Landmarks, Commission on (1964)
  Chicago Architectural Photographing Co. (1956, 1958, 1966)
  Chicago, Art Institute of (1937, 1944, 1945, 1951, 1960, 1978) (see also: Art Institute of Chicago; Burnham Library Ryerson; Burnham Libraries)
  Chicago, Arts Club of (1951-1952)
  Chicago Committee on Architectural Landmarks (1960)
  Chicago Historical and Architectural Landmarks, Commission on (1969-1970, 1973, 1975)
  Chicago School of Architecture Foundation (1967)
  Chicago, University of (1947, 1953, 1957, 1961-1962, 1973, 1986) (see also: University of Chicago)
  Chickering, A. H. (1954)
  Childs, Charles D. (1951-1952, 1955)
  Childs, Maurice F. (1952, 1955)
  Chittenden, A. J. (1947)
  Christian Science Monitor (1948)
  Christiansen, Erwin O. (1946)
  Christmas Cards (1952, 1983, undated)
  Church, Robert M. (1951-1952, 1954-1955)
  Churchill, Agnes (1948)
  Cincinnati (1969)
  Cincinnati Art Museum (1955-1956, 1960-1961)
  Cincinnati Astronomical Society (1935)
  Cincinnati Modern Art Society (1948)
  Cincinnati, University of (1966)
  Cistercian Order (1958)
  City Art Museum of St. Louis (see: St. Louis, City Art Museum of)
  City University of New York (1970, 1974-1976, 1978)
  City [of Springfield, Mass.] Library Association (1954)
  Ciucci, Giorgio (1970)
  Claflin, Agnes Rindge (1948-1949, 1952, 1956, 1959, 1961, 1966, 1973, 1977-1978) (see also: Rindge, Agnes)
  Clapp, Verner W. (1953)
  Clark Art Institute (1973, 1986)
  Clark, G. R. (1946)
  Clark, James (1973)
  Clark, Orton Loring (1952)
  Clark, Robert J. (1960, 1963-1971, 1974-1975, 1980)
  Clark, Ronald W. (1956)
  Clark, Susan (1975)
  Clark, Willene B. (1976)
  Clarke, M. L. (1962)
  Clarke, Marian (1947-1948, 1950)
  Clarke, Peter (1946)
  Clausen, Meredith (1987)
  Clayton, B. D. (1971-1972)
  Clayton, Barry (1965)
  Clerehan, Neil (1953)
  Clews, Mrs. Henry (1955)
  Clifton-Raymond Associates (1968)
  Clifton-Taylor, Alec (1984)
  Clinton [Conn.] Historical Society (1947)
  Close, Elizabeth (1960)
  Clough, R. T. (1959)
  Club of Odd Volumes (1948-1950, 1952-1957, 1961-1965, 1968-1970)
  Cochrane, Alexander S. (1947, 1951-1954)
  Cochrane, Alexander and Cally (1950)
  Cochrane, Mr. and Mrs. E. W. (1953)
  Cochrane, Eric (1964)
  Cochrane, Eric and Lydia (1956, 1983, 1985)
  Cochrane, Lydia (1955, 1959, 1960-1963, 1965, 1967, 1970-1971, 1975, 1977-1978, 1980-1982, 1984, 1986)
  Coddington, John (1945-1949, 1951, 1956-1957, 1959, 1961-1962, 1968-1970, 1977, undated)
  Coe, Bill (1958)
  Coe, R. E. (Ted) (1962)
  Coe, Ralph T. (1953, 1955, 1974)
  Coffin, David R. (1965, 1968, 1973)
  Cogswell, Dorothy (1951, 1959, 1962)
  Cohen, Alfred (1946)
  Cohen, Joan L. (1954-1957, 1960, 1963-1965)
  Cohn, David N. (1984)
  Cohn, Suzanne (1968)
  Colby College (1968)
  Cole, Dorothy (1958)
  Cole, Harry (1957)
  Coletti, Joseph (1961)
  Coletti, Paul (1957)
  Colgate University (1976, 1978)
  Colibris Editora Ltda. (1962, 1964-1965, 1967)
  Colin, Mrs. Ralph F. ( 1955)
  Collaborazione Culturale, Instituto per la (1962)
  College Art Association (1940, 1946-1953, 1955-1959, 1961-1964, 1966, 1969-1971, 1973-1979)
  Colliers Encyclopedia (1947-1949, 1958-1959)
  Collins, Cecil (1956)
  Collins, Colin (1955)
  Collins, Elizabeth (1959)
  Collins, George R. (1960-1961, 1964, 1968, 1975-1976, 1979, 1983)
  Collins, Peter (1964-1965, 1967-1968)
  Colonial Travel Bureau (1955)
  Columbia Historical Society (1982)
  Columbia University 1937, 1939-1941, 1945, 1947-1948, 1954-1956, 1958-1959, 1961, 1964-1969, 1971, 1973-1977, 1979-1983, 1985-1986 (see also: Avery Library; Avery Study Center, Columbia University)
  Columbia University, Temple Hoyle Buell Center for the Study of American Architecture (1984)
  Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts (1948-1949)
  Colvin, Howard M. (1959)
  Colwell, Miriam (1976)
  Combs, Tom (1975)
  Comite Francais D'Historie de L'Art (1967)
  Commercial Credit Corporation (1947)
  Committee for the Centennial Exhibition of New England Architecture (1957)
  Committee for the Preservation of Architectural Records (1979)
  Committee on Education and Labor, U. S. Congress (1954)
  Committee on Government and Art (see: Government and Art, Committee on)
  Community Arts Center (1945)
  Community Chest (1958)
  Comparative Studies in Society and History (1958)
  Conant, Kenneth G. (1946-1947, 1952, 1973)
  Concrete Quarterly (1955)
  Condit, Carl W. (1963)
  Condolence Letters [on death of mother] (1952)
  Conference Board of Associated Research Councils (1948, 1951)
  Congress on the History of Art, Twentieth International (1960-1961)
  Conlon, Kathleen M. (1969)
  Connaissance des Artes (1959)
  Connecticut Automobile Assigned Risk Plan (1946-1947)
  Connecticut College (1938-1942, 1944, 1947, 1953, 1956, 1963, undated)
  Connecticut Commission on the Arts (1968)
  Connecticut, Department of Agriculture (1937)
  Connecticut State Department of Consumer Protection (1986)
  Connecticut, State of (1946, 1948)
  Connecticut, University of (1952, 1963)
  Connecticut Valley Historical Museum (1954)
  Connors, Joseph (1984)
  Constable, Olivia (1955)
  Constable, W. G. (1952-1953)
  Constantine, Mildred (1952, 1955, 1960-1961, 1963)
  Contemporary Authors (1978)
  Cook, R. V. ( 1946)
  Cook, Ruth (1952, 1956)
  Cook, Mrs. Sidney (1950)
  Cook, Thomas (1956-1957)
  Cook, Walter (1946-1947, 1949-1956, 1958)
  Cooke, Howard Lester (1954-1955)
  Cookson, Beatrice (1970)
  Coolidge, Harold (1956)
  Coolidge, John (1939-1941, 1944-1945, 1950-1951, 1953-1956, 1958, 1960-1962, 1966, 1968, 1973-1974, 1976, 1978-1979, 1983, undated)
  Coolidge, John and Polly (1947-1949, 1969, 1977)
  Coolidge, Polly (1952)
  Cooper (1952)
  Cooper, Douglas (1947, 1953, 1960)
  Cooper-Hewitt Museum (1972-1973, 1975, 1979-1980, 1983)
  Cooper Union (1946-1948, 1955, 1964-1965, 1968)
  Copp, Philip (1979)
  Copplestone, Lewin (1972)
  Corcoran, Desmond (1981)
  Corcoran, G. S. (1946)
  Corcoran, Gerald (1952)
  Cordes, Paul (1945)
  Cordingley, Alan (1957, 1961)
  Cordingly, Ann (1975)
  Corke, Jean (1962)
  Corkran, W. S. (1954-1955)
  Cornell University (1946, 1964-1966, 1969, 1976)
  Corning Glass Center (1952)
  Cortetti, John (1952)
  Costabel, Jorge (1956)
  Costopoulos, Dorothy (1973-1975)
  Cott, Perry B. (1946, 1949)
  Country Life (1952-1954, 1956, 1958, 1962-1963)
  Courtauld Institute of Art (1966)
  Court House (1979)
  Courtright, Margot (1978)
  Covell, William King (1936, 1946, 1948-1952, 1958, 1962-1963, 1965, 1968)
  Coventry Architecture and Planning Department (1955)
  Cowdrey, Mary Bartlett (1951, 1952-1955, 1958-1965, 1968, 1973-1974)
  Cowin, Ruth (1962)
  Cowles, Mr. and Mrs. Gardner (1975)
  Cowles, William S. (1952)
  Cowling, Francis B. (1949-1950)
  Cox, Harvey (1970)
  Cox, Trenchard (1952, 1956)
  Cox, Warren (1957)
  Craig, Maurice James (1949)
  Cranbrook Academy and Museum of Art (1982, 1984)
  Crandall, Robert T. (1959)
  Crane, Alexander (1949, 1951)
  Crane, Tom (1980)
  Crapanzano, Frank (1947)
  Craven, Wayne (1962)
  Crawford, Martha (1958)
  Creative Art (1928)
  Creese, Walter (1945, 1950-1954, 1956, 1960-1962, 1968-1969)
  Criticism (1961)
  Crivelli Galleria (1960)
  Crook, Joseph Mordaunt (1975, 1981, 1983)
  Crosby, Sumner (1951-1952, 1958-1959)
  Crowe, R. N. (1956)
  Crowell Co. (1967)
  Crowell, Frederick (1962-1963)
  Crystal Palace (1954)
  Cubitt, James (1952, 1966)
  Cucci, Ditta (1966)
  Culpepper, Ralph (1966)
  Cultural Center, New York (1974)
  Cummings, Abbott Lowell (1947, 1951, 1956, 1964)
  Cunard Lines (1949, 1973, 1976)
  Cunill, Titit (1973, 1974)
  Cunningham, Charles C. (1945, 1947-1948, 1957, 1962, 1964, undated)
  Cunningham, Charles C. and Priscilla (1958, 1961, 1968)
  Cunningham, E. (1963)
  Cunningham, Priscilla (1959-1960, 1973) (see also:
  Cunningham, Charles C. and Priscilla)
  Curjel, Hans (1952)
  Curtis, L. P. (1952)
  Curtis, Louis (1967)
  Custom Shop (1946, 1953)
  Customs 1947, (1948, 1952, 1958-1959)
  Cutting, Gloria P. (1950)
  Czech, Hermann (1969)
  Dabrowski, Magdalena (1973)
  Da Capo Press, Inc. (1974, 1976)
  Dahl, Curtis (1975, 1978)
  D'Amato, Alfonse M. (1986)
  Dame, Bernard L. (1949)
  Dane, William J. (1955, 1957)
  Danes, Gibson (1947-1958, 1961, 1966, 1972)
  Danish Architectural Press (1962)